

RIZWANUL ISLAM RUDRA

UX Designer & Web Developer



PROFILE

I am a passionate Web Developer and UX designer based in Bangkok, Thailand. I have been staying in Bangkok for four years and studying Computer Engineering in Assumption University (ABAC), the first international university of I love to play with different Thailand. programming languages and frameworks. Experienced in UI/UX designing and Application Architecture. Besides the software field I am also experienced in IoT & Embedded Systems. Fluent in English and can speak basic Thai.



OBJECTIVE

Seeking full time job in the field of Computer Engineering / IT / Web Development or any interesting work field.



PERSONAL SKILL

MANAGEMENT TEAMWORK CREATIVE





CONTACT ME

- 249 Sapsin1, Ramkhamhaeng Soi 24, Yak 34, Huamark, Bangkapi, Bangkok 10240
- 0900152360
- rizwanulrudra@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/pub/rizwanul-islam-rudra/ba/a26/876



EDUCATION

June 2011-May 2016

ASSUMPTION UNIVERSITY OF THAILAND

Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.)

Major: Computer Engineering Concentration: Computer Systems

CGPA: 2.68/4.0

Course Projects: Smart Car Parking System, Tour Expense Tracking System, Water Level Monitoring System (With Google Map API)

Senior Project: AU QUAD-71 Smart drone for Agriculture and data analysis.



EXPERIENCE

June 2015-Present

TASTE OF THAILAND FOOD TOURS

Bangkok, Thailand

Social Media Manager & Web Development (Internship)

Roles:

- Managing various social media platforms like facebook, twitter, pinterest etc.
- Blog and content writing for the website.
- Developing company website and IT support.
- Building web applications.

April 2015-January 2016

AIRPORTS OF THAILAND PCL

Suvarnabhumi Airport, Bangkok

ASQ Survey Agent (Internship) Roles:

• Collecting surveys from the local and international passengers on departure and analyze them perfectly.



PROGRAMMING SKILL

HTML5	
CSS3	
JAVASCRIPT	
PHP	
PYTHON	
MYSQL	
C	
JAVA	
WORDPRESS	
WORDFRESS	



DESIGNING SKILL

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR IN DESIGN